Guys? There's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
Wait, wait. What is that?
That's Marcel. Wanna say hi?
No, I don't.
He is precious!
Where did you get him?
My friend Bethel rescued him
from some lab.
That is so cruel.
Why? Why would a parent
name their child Bethel?
That monkey's got a Ross on his ass!
Is he gonna live with you,
like, in your apartment?
It's been kind of quiet
since Carol left, so. . . .
Why don't you just get a roommate?
I don't know.
You reach a certain age. . .
. . .having a roommate
is just kind of pathe--
Sorry, that's ''pathet,'' which is
Sanskrit for ''cool way to live. ''
The One With the Monkey
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
I'm doing all-new material tonight.
I have 12 new songs about my mother's
suicide and one about a snowman.
Might want to open with the snowman.
So how'd it go?
I didn't get the job.
How could you not get it?
You were Santa last year!
I don't know. Some fat guy's
sleeping with the store manager.
He's not even jolly.
It's all political.
What are you gonna be?
I'm gonna be one of his helpers.
It's just such a slap in the face,
you know?
Hey, do you guys know
what you're doing for New Year's?
Hey, what? What is wrong
with New Year's?
Nothing for you. You have Paolo.
You don't have to face the pressure. . .
. . .of finding anything with lips
to kiss when the ball drops!
Man, I'm talking loud!
For your information, Paolo's
gonna be in Rome this New Year's.
I'll be just as pathetic
as the rest of you.
Yeah, you wish.
I'm sick of being a victim
this Dick Clark holiday.
I say this year, no dates,
we make a pact.
Just the six of us. Dinner.
-Sure.
-Fine.
I was hoping for a little
more enthusiasm.
You're on.
Oh, good.
Okay, hi. Ladies and gentlemen,
back by popular demand. . .
. . .Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks. Hi.
I want to start with a song that
means a lot to me this time of year.
I made a man with eyes of coal
And a smile so bewitchin '
How was I supposed to know
That my mom was dead in the kitchen?
My mother's ashes
Even her eyelashes
Are resting in a little yellow jar
And sometimes when it's freezing
I feel a little sneezy
And now I--
Excuse me? Excuse me?
Noisy boys.
Is it something you'd like
to share with the group?
No, that's okay.
If it's important enough
to discuss while I'm playing. . .
. . .I assume it's important enough
for everyone else to hear.
That guy's going home with a note.
-I was just saying--
-Could you speak up?
Sorry.
I was saying you were
the most beautiful woman I'd ever seen.
And you said Daryl Hannah. . .
. . .was the most beautiful woman
he'd ever seen.
And I said I liked her in Splash,
but not in Wall Street.
-I thought she had a hard quality.
-A hard quality.
And while Daryl Hannah is beautiful
in a conventional way. . .
. . .you are luminous
with a kind of delicate grace.
Then that's when you started yelling.
Okay, we're gonna take a short break.
I think that guy's going home
with more than a note.
Come here, Marcel. Sit here.
Pheebs, I can't believe
he hasn't kissed you yet.
I mean, by my sixth date with Paolo,
he'd already named both my breasts.
Did I just share too much?
Just a smidge.
David's, like, a scientist guy.
He's very methodical.
I think it's romantic.
Me too!
Did you ever see
An Officer and a Gentleman?
He's kind of like the guy
I went to see that with.
Except he's smarter and gentler
and sweeter.
I just want to be
with him all the time.
You know, day and night.
And night and day.
And special occasions.
I see where this is going.
You're gonna ask him to New Year's.
You'll break the pact.
She's breaking the pact.
Yeah, could I just. . .?
Yeah, because I already asked Janice.
Come on, this was a pact!
This was your pact!
I couldn't handle the pressure
and I snapped!
But Janice?
That was the worst breakup in history!
I'm not saying it was a good idea.
I snapped!
Hi, sorry I'm late.
Too many jokes.
Must mock Joey.
Nice shoes, huh?
God, you're killing me!
He's playing with my spatulas again!
Look, he's not gonna hurt them, right?
Do you always have to bring him here?
I didn't want to leave him alone.
We had our first fight this morning.
It has to do with my working late.
I said some things that I didn't mean.
He threw some feces.
If you're working late,
I can look in on him.
That would be great!
But make sure it seems
like you're there to see him. . .
. . .and you're not doing it
as a favor to me.
Okay. But if he asks,
I'm not going to lie.
But you can't actually
test this theory.
Because today's particle accelerators
are nowhere near powerful enough. . .
. . .to simulate these conditions.
All right. I have a question then.
Were you planning on kissing me ever?
That's definitely a valid question. . .
. . .and the answer. . .
. . .would be yes.
Yes, I was.
But see, I wanted it to be
this phenomenal kiss. . .
. . .that happened at this
phenomenal moment because it's you.
Sure.
Right. But the longer I waited,
the more phenomenal the kiss had to be.
And now, it's just got to be
one of those things where I. . .
. . .sweep everything off the table
and throw you down on it.
And I'm not really
a sweeping sort of fella.
Oh, David, I think you are
a ''sweeping sort of fella. ''
I mean, you're a sweeper
trapped inside a physicist's body.
-Really.
-I'm sure of it.
You should just do it.
Just sweep and throw me.
Now?
Right now. Just. . . .
You know what?
This is just really expensive.
And this was a gift.
-Now you're just tidying up.
-Okay, what the hell?
-You want me to actually throw you--?
-I can hop.
Tell me something, what does
''No-Date Pact'' mean to you?
I'm sorry. It's just that Chandler
has somebody and Phoebe has somebody.
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
Fun Bobby, your ex-boyfriend,
Fun Bobby?
You know more than one Fun Bobby?
I happen to know a Fun Bob.
Okay. Here we go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
There's no room for milk.
There. Now there is.
So on our no-date evening, three
of you now are gonna have dates.
-Four.
-Five.
Sorry. Paolo's catching
an earlier flight.
And I met this really hot
single mom at the store.
What's an elf to do?
So I'm gonna be the only one standing
there alone when the ball drops?
Come on. We'll have a big party,
and no one will know who's with who.
This is so not what I needed now.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's Marcel.
He keeps shutting me out.
He's walking around all the time,
dragging his hands.
That's weird. I had a blast
with him the other night.
-Really?
-We played. We watched TV.
That juggling thing is amazing.
What juggling thing?
With the balled-up socks?
I figured you taught him that.
It wasn't that big a deal.
Just balled-up socks.
And a melon.
-Phoebe! Hi!
-Hi, Max. Do you know everybody?
No. Have you seen David?
No, he hasn't been around.
If you see him, tell him to pack.
We are going to Minsk.
Minsk?
Minsk. It's in Russia.
I know where Minsk is.
We got the grant!
Three years, all expenses paid.
So when do you leave?
January 1 st.
-What are you doing here?
-Max told me about Minsk.
So, you know, congratulations!
This is so exciting!
It'd be even more exciting,
if we were going.
Oh, you're not going? Oh, why?
Tell her, David.
''I don't want to go to Minsk to work
with Lipson and Yamaguchi and Flank.
I want to stay here and make out
with my girlfriend! ''
Okay, thank you, Max.
Thank you.
So you're really not going?
I don't know. I don't know
what I'm gonna do. I just. . . .
You decide.
-Don't do that.
-Please?
But I'm asking you.
I can't make a decision.
-Please, just--
-Okay. Stay.
-Stay.
Getting so good at that!
It was Max's stuff.
I love this artichoke thing.
Don't tell me what's in it.
The diet starts tomorrow.
You remember Janice.
Vividly.
Hi, I'm Sandy.
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
You brought your kids.
Yeah. That's okay, right?
Party!
That thing is not coming in here!
''That thing''? This is how
you greet guests at a party?
If I showed up with my new girlfriend,
she wouldn't be welcome?
Your new girlfriend
wouldn't urinate on my coffee table.
He was more embarrassed
about that than anyone.
And for him to have the courage
to walk back in here. . .
. . .like nothing happened. . . .
All right. All right.
Just keep him away from me.
Thank you. Come on, Marcel.
What do you say you and I
do a little mingling?
All right. . .
. . .I'll catch up with you later.
Oh, my God! Rachel, honey. . .
. . .are you okay?
Where's Paolo?
Rome.
Jerk missed his flight.
And then your face exploded?
I was at the airport
getting into a cab. . .
. . .when this woman. . .
. . .this blond planet
with a pocketbook. . .
. . .starts yelling at me.
Something about how
it was her cab first.
The next thing I know, she just
starts pulling me out by my hair!
And I started blowing my attack
whistle thingy. . .
. . .and then three more cabs show up.
So as I'm going to get into a cab,
she tackles me!
And I hit my head on the curb
and cut my lip on my whistle.
Everybody having fun at the party?
Are people eating my dip?
When I saw you at the store
last week. . .
. . .it was probably the first time
I ever mentally undressed an elf.
Wow, that's dirty!
Hey, kids.
Look at him. I'm not saying he has
to spend the whole evening with me. . .
. . .but at least check in.
There you are!
You got away from me.
But you found me.
Here, Ross, take our picture.
Smile. You're on Janice Camera.
Kill me. Kill me now.
Everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
Hey, sorry I'm late.
But my grandfather. . .
. . .died about two hours ago.
But I couldn't get a flight
out till tomorrow, so. . .
. . .here I am.
Hey, Fun Bobby!
How's it going, man?
Whoa! Who died?
It's going to be an open casket,
you know?
So at least I'll get to see him again.
I'm gonna blow this one up and
I'm gonna write ''Reunited'' in glitter.
All right, Janice, that's it!
When I invited you, I didn't
think it meant that we--
Oh, no!
-I'm sorry you misunderstood.
-Oh, my God!
You listen to me!
One of these times, it's just gonna be
your last chance with me!
Will you give me the thing?
Hi, Max.
Yoko.
I've decided to go to Minsk
without you.
It won't be the same. . .
. . .but it will still be Minsk.
Happy New Year.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
You're going to Minsk.
No, I'm not going to Minsk.
Oh, you are so going to Minsk.
You belong in Minsk.
You can't stay here just for me.
Yes, I can. Because if I go,
it means I have to break up with you.
-And I can't break up with you.
-Oh, yes. Yes, you can.
Just say, ''Phoebe, I love you,
but my work is my life.
That's what I have to do now. ''
And I say, ''Your work?
How can you say that?''
And then you say,
''It's tearing me apart. . .
. . .but I have no choice.
Can't you understand that?''
And I say, ''No!
No! I can't understand that! ''
Sorry.
And then you put
your arms around me. . . .
Put your arms around me.
Sorry.
And then you tell me you love me
and you'll never forget me.
I'll never forget you.
Then you say that it's almost
midnight and you have to go. . .
. . .because you don't want to start
the year with me if you can't finish it.
I'm gonna miss you. . .
. . .you scientist guy.
Hi, this is Dick Clark live
in Times Square.
We're in a virtual snowstorm
of confetti here in Times Square.
It gets better every year.
Here you go, kids.
And then the peacock bit me.
Please kiss me at midnight!
You seen Sandy?
I don't know how to tell you this. . .
. . .but she's in the bedroom getting it
on with Max, that scientist geek.
Cool, look at that.
I did know how to tell you.
Hey, everybody, the ball is going.
What?
The ball is dropping!
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
And the moment of joy is upon us.
Looks like that ''No-Date Pact'' thing
worked out.
Everybody looks so happy.
I hate that!
Not everybody is happy.
Hey, Bobby!
--four, three, two. . .
. . .one! Happy New Year!
I just thought I'd throw this out.
I'm no math whiz. . .
. . .but I do believe there are
three girls and three guys right here.
I don't feel like kissing
anyone tonight.
I can't kiss anyone.
So I'm kissing everyone?
You can't kiss Ross.
That's your brother.
Perfect. So now everybody's
getting kissed but me.
Somebody kiss me.
Somebody kiss me! It's midnight!
All right! All right! All right!
There!
I wanted this to work so much.
I'm still in there, you know?
Changing his diapers.
Picking his fleas.
But he's just phoning it in.
It's hard to accept
that something you love so much. . .
. . .doesn't love you back, you know?
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.