Coffee.
-Thank you.
-Cappuccino.
And a nice hot cider for Monica.
Thank you.
Rach?
Why does my cinnamon stick
have an eraser?
That's why.
Sorry.
The One With the Stoned Guy
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Chandler?
Miss Tedlock, you're looking
lovely today.
May I say that is a very
flattering sleeve length on you?
Mr. Costilick would like you to stop
by his office at the end of the day.
If this is about those prank memos,
I had nothing to do with them.
Nothing at all. Really.
Nothing.
Hey, you guys! You guys!
Chandler's coming and he says
he has incredible news.
So when he gets here,
let's all act, like, you know--
Never mind. But it was gonna
be really good.
What's going on?
So it's a typical day at work.
I'm inputting my numbers. . .
. . .and Big Al tells me he wants
to make me processing supervisor.
-That is great!
-Congratulations!
So. . .
. . .I quit.
Why?
Why? This was supposed to be
a temp job.
Chandler, you've been there
for five years.
I know, but if I took it, it would
be admitting that this is what I do.
Was it a lot more money?
Doesn't matter. I just don't want
to be a guy who sits in his office. . .
. . .worrying about the WENUS.
''The WENUS?''
Weekly estimated net usage system.
It's a processing term.
Oh, that WENUS.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know. That's the thing.
But I won't figure it out
working there.
I have something you can do!
I have this new massage client, Steve.
Anyway, he's opening up
a restaurant. . .
. . .and he's looking for a head chef.
Hi, there.
I know. You're a chef, I know,
and I thought of you first.
But Chandler's the one
who needs a job right now, so. . . .
I just don't have a lot
of chefing experience.
Unless it's an all-toast restaurant.
What kind of food
is he looking for?
He wants to do something eclectic,
so he's looking for someone. . .
. . .who can create the entire menu.
-Oh, my God!
-Yeah, I know!
So what do you think?
Thanks. I just don't see myself
in a big white hat.
Oh, Monica! Guess what?
Can you see my nipples
through this shirt?
No, but don't worry.
I'm sure they're still there.
Where you going, Mr. Suit-ey Man?
I have an appointment to see Dr. Robert
Pilman, career counselor-a-go-go!
I added the ''a-go-go. ''
Career counselor?
Hey, you guys all know
what you want to do.
I don't.
Hey, you guys in the living room
all know what you want to do.
You know, you have goals,
you have dreams.
I don't have a dream!
The lesser known
''I Don't Have a Dream'' speech.
Oh, I love my life! I love my life!
Brian 's Song!
The meeting went great?
So great! He showed me
where the restaurant's gonna be.
It's this cute little place on 1 0th.
It's not too big, not too small.
It's just right.
Was it formerly owned
by a blond woman and some bears?
Anyway, I'm cooking for him
Monday night. Kind of an audition.
He wants you to be here,
which will be great for me.
You can make yummy noises.
-What are you gonna make?
-Yummy noises.
And, Monica, what are you gonna make?
I don't know.
It's just got to be great.
I know what you can make!
I know!
You should make that thing
with the stuff.
You know. . .
. . .that thing with the stuff?
Okay, I don't know.
Anyone know a good date place
in the neighborhood?
How about Tony's? If you can finish
a 32-ounce steak, it's free.
Anyone know a good place
if you're not dating a puma?
-Who are you going out with?
-Is this the bug lady?
I love you, Ross.
Her name's Celia.
She's not a bug lady.
She's curator of insects
at the museum.
What are you gonna do?
I thought we'd go to dinner,
then bring her back to my place. . .
. . .and I'd introduce her to my monkey.
He's not speaking metaphorically.
So back to your place?
You thinking maybe. . . .
Well, I don't know. . . .
I'm hoping. . . .
I tell you, that monkey's
a chick magnet.
She's gonna look at his furry, cute
little face and it'll seal the deal.
Celia, don't worry.
He's not gonna hurt you!
Soothing tones, soothing tones.
Here, here.
You want some?
I can't stand this.
He's got his claws on my--
Yeah, all right.
Try this salmon mousse.
Good.
Is it better than
the other salmon mousse?
It's creamier.
Yeah? Well, is that better?
I don't know.
We're talking about whipped fish.
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
God, what happened to you?
Eight and a half hours
of aptitude tests. . .
. . .intelligence tests, personality
tests, and what do I learn?
''You're suited for data processing for
a large multi national corporation. ''
That's so great because you
already know how to do that!
Can you believe it?
Don't I seem like I should
be doing something really cool?
You know, I just always
pictured myself doing something. . . .
Something!
Oh, Chandler, I know, I know.
You can see your nipples
through this shirt.
Here you go.
Maybe this will cheer you up.
I had a grape about five hours ago,
so I better split this with you.
It's supposed to be that small.
It's a pre-appetizer.
The French call it an amuse-bouche.
Well, it is amusing.
Oh, hi, Wendy.
Yeah, 8:00.
What did we say, $ 1 0 an hour?
Okay, great.
All right, I'll see you then. Bye.
Ten dollars an hour for what?
I asked a waitress at work
to help me out.
Waitressing?
Of course I thought of you.
But. . . .
But, but. . . .
But, you see, it's just this thing
has to go just perfect, you know. . .
. . .and, well, Wendy's more
of a professional waitress.
And I'm maintaining my amateur status
so I can waitress in the Olympics.
You know, I don't mean to brag, but
I waited tables at lnnsbruck in '7 6.
Amuse-bouche?
Talk to me.
A weird thing happened to me
on the train this morning--
Talk dirty.
-Here?
-Come on.
Come on.
Say something. . .
. . .hot!
What?
-What?
-Vulva.
''Vulva?''
All right, I panicked, all right?
She took me by surprise.
But it wasn't a total loss.
I mean, we ended up cuddling.
Whoa, you cuddled? How many times?
Shut up. It was nice.
I just don't think I'm
the dirty-talking kind of guy.
Just say what you want to do to her.
Or what you want her to do to you.
Or what you think other people
might be doing to each other.
Look, I tell you what.
Try something on me.
Please be kidding.
Why not? Come on.
Just close your eyes and tell me
what you'd like to be doing right now.
I'm in my apartment. . . .
Yeah, what else?
You're not there.
We're not having this conversation!
-All right. I'll start.
-Joey, please.
Come on, come on.
All right, ready?
Oh, Ross. . .
. . .you get me so hot,
I want your lips on me now.
See?
Now you say something.
I really don't think so.
Come on.
You like this woman?
-You wanna see her again?
-Sure.
If you can't talk dirty to me,
how will you talk dirty to her?
Now tell me you want
to caress my butt!
Okay, turn around.
I don't want you staring at me
while I do this.
All right, all right.
I'm not looking. Go ahead.
Okay.
I want--
Okay, I want. . .
. . .to feel. . .
. . .your hot, soft skin
with my lips.
There you go.
Keep going, keep going.
I want to take my tongue and--
Say it.
Say it!
--run it all over your body. . .
. . .until you're trembling with--
With?
-Funny story.
-You're not gonna believe this.
It's okay. It's okay.
I was always rooting for you
two kids to get together.
While you were sleeping, that guy
from your old job called again.
Again?
-And again and again and again.
-And again.
And again!
Hey, Mr. Costilick.
How's life on the 1 5th floor?
Yeah, I miss you too.
It's a lot less satisfying
to steal pens from your own home.
That's very generous.
But look, this isn't about the money.
I need something more than a job.
I need something I really care about--
That's on top of the year-end
bonus structure?
-Your dream!
Look, Al. Al, I'm not
playing hardball here, okay?
This is not a negotiation.
This is a rejection!
Stop saying numbers!
I'm telling you, you've got
the wrong guy! You got the wrong guy!
I'll see you Monday!
Wow! It's huge!
It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
This is a cube!
Look at this.
You have a window!
Yes, indeedy.
-With a beautiful view of--
-Oh, look! That guy's peeing!
Okay. That's enough of the view.
Check this out.
Okay, sit down here. Sit down.
This is great. This is great.
You ready?
Helen, could you come in here
for a moment?
Thank you, that'll be all.
Last time I do that.
I promise.
Wendy, we had a deal.
Yeah, you promised.
Who was that?
Wendy bailed.
I have no waitress.
That's too bad.
Bye-bye.
-Ten dollars an hour!
-Nope.
$ 1 2 an hour.
I wish I could, but I've made plans
to walk around.
When you ran out on your wedding,
I was there for you.
I put a roof over your head,
and if that means nothing to you. . . .
Twenty dollars an hour.
Done.
Well, hello! Welcome to Monica's!
May I take your coat?
-Hi, Steve.
-Hello, Monica.
Hello, greeter girl.
-This is Rachel.
-Yeah, okay.
Everything smells so delicious.
I can't remember a time I smelled
such a delicious combination of--
Okay, smells.
It's a lovely apartment.
Thank you. Would you like a tour?
I was just being polite,
but all right.
What's up?
In the cab on the way over,
Steve blazed up a doobie.
What?
Smoked a joint, you know?
Lit a bone. Weed, hemp, ganja.
Okay, I'm with you, Cheech.
Is it dry in here?
Let me get you some wine.
I think we're ready
for our first course too.
These are rock shrimp ravioli. . .
. . .in a cilantro ponzu sauce. . .
. . .with just a touch of minced. . .
. . .ginger.
Well, smack my ass and call me Judy!
These are fantastic!
Oh, gosh! I'm so glad you liked them.
Like them? I couId eat 100 of them!
That's all there is of these. . .
. . .but in about 8 1 /2 minutes,
we'll serve some tartlets.
''Tartlets?''
''Tartlets. ''
Word has lost all meaning.
Excuse me. Can I help you
with anything?
You know, I don't know
what I'm looking for.
Oh, cool! Taco shells!
These are-- They are like a little
corn envelope, you know?
You don't want to spoil your appetite.
Sugar-O's!
You know, if you just wait
another 6 1 /2 minutes--
Macaroni and cheese!
We gotta make this!
No, we don't.
Sorry.
Why don't you just have a seat here?
Give me the Gummy Bears.
Give them to me.
We'll share.
-No. Give me the bears.
-You can't have any.
Give them to me!
This is not working.
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
Hey, fellas! Grab onto a Sugar-O!
Save yourselves!
Help! Help! I'm drowning! Help!
That's it! Dinner is over!
-What?
-''What?''
-Why?
-''Why?''
I've waited seven years
for an opportunity like this. . .
. . .and you can't even wait
4 1/2 minutes for a tartlet?
What a tool.
You don't want to work
for a guy like that.
I know. It's just I just thought
that this was, you know, ''it. ''
You'll get there.
You're an amazing chef.
You know those yummy noises?
I wasn't faking.
So how did it go with Celia?
I was unbelievable.
All right, Ross!
I was the James Michener
of dirty talk.
It was the most elaborate filth
you have ever heard.
I mean, there were characters,
plot lines. . .
. . .themes, a motif.
At one point, there were villagers.
And. . . .
Well, by the time we finished
with all the dirty talk. . .
. . .it was late and we were
both exhausted, so. . . .
-You cuddled.
-Yeah, which was nice.
Do you guys want to try to catch
a late movie?
Shouldn't we wait for Chandler?
Whoa! Where the hell is he?
Yes, Fran, I know what time it is. . .
. . .but I'm looking at the WENUS
and I'm not happy!
Oh, really?
Let me tell you something.
You will care about it because
I care about it. Got it? Good!
How's this?
Sorry. How about over here?
That just means it's working.
Does this hurt?
How about this?
There you go!
Oh, the throb!