Okay, I checked.
We have EarI Grey, EngIish Breakfast,
cinnamon stick. . .
. . .chamomiIe, Mint MedIey,
bIackberry and. . . .
Wait, there's one more. . . .
Lemon Soother!
You're not the guy that asked
for the tea, are you?
The One Where the Monkey Gets Away
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Mail call!
Rachel Greene, bunk seven.
Thank you.
Oh, cool!
A free sample of coffee.
Oh, good, because
where else would we get any?
Oh, right.
Great.
What is it?
Country club newsletter.
My mother sends me the engagement
notices for inspiration.
Oh, my God!
It's Barry and Mindy!
-Barry, who you almost--?
-Barry, who I almost--
-And Mindy, your maid of--
-Mindy, my maid of--
Let me see.
That's Mindy?
Wow! She is pretty.
Lucky. . .
. . .to have had a friend like you.
Marcel, bring me the rice.
Come on, bring me the rice.
Good boy.
Give me the rice.
Thank you. Good boy.
He's mastered the difference
between ''bring me the'' . . .
. . .and ''pee in the. ''
''Bring me the'' and--
Rach?
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is so stupid!
I mean, I gave Barry up, right?
I should be happy for them.
I am. I'm happy for them.
Really?
I guess it would be different
if I were with somebody.
Whoa, what. . . .
What happened to
''Forget relationships!
I'm done with men''?
The whole penis embargo?
I don't know.
I guess it's not about ''no guys. ''
It's about the ''right guy,''
you know?
With Barry. . .
. . .it was safe and it was easy,
but there was no heat.
With Paolo, all there was, was heat.
And I mean, it was just
this raw, animal, sexual--
Right, right! I got it.
I was there.
But do you think
you can ever have both?
Someone that's your best friend. . .
. . .but then also can make
your toes curl.
Yes, I do. I really do.
In fact, it's funny.
Often, someone who
you wouldn't think could. . .
. . .curl your toes. . .
. . .might just be the one who--
--gets interrupted.
Hey, guys, how was the movie?
-Wonderful!
-It was so good!
-Suck fest.
-Total chick flick.
I'm sorry it wasn't one of those
movies with, like, guns and bombs. . .
. . .and buses going really fast!
I don't need violence
to enjoy a movie. . .
. . .as long as
there's a little nudity.
There was nudity.
I meant female nudity.
I don't need to see
Lou Grant frolicking.
Hugh! Hugh Grant!
All right, I've got to go.
Come on, Marcel.
Come on!
We're gonna go take a bath.
Yes, we are, aren't we?
They're still just friends, right?
And I will see you tomorrow.
Right. You're gonna spend
tomorrow at Aunt Rachel's.
Hang on. Does Aunt Monica
get a say in this?
Please, Aunt Monica, please?
Oh, unclench.
You won't even be here.
I can't believe
we're having this discussion.
I agree.
I'm, like, in disbelief.
If it was gonna happen
with Rachel. . .
. . .wouldn't it
have happened already?
She said she's looking
for a relationship. . .
. . .with someone exactly like me.
She said that?
Well, I added
the ''exactly like me'' part.
But she said
she's looking for someone.
And someone will be there tonight.
''Tonight'' tonight?
It's perfect.
It'll just be the two of us.
She spent all day
taking care of my monkey.
I can't remember the last time
a girl took care of my monkey.
Anyway, I figured after work,
I'd go pick up a bottle of wine. . .
. . .go over there
and try to woo her.
You know what you should do?
Take her back to the 1 890s
when that phrase was last used.
If you keep this up...
... you'll be finished
by the weekend.
Now, the one in the feathered boa,
that's Dr. Francis.
Now, she used to be a man.
Look. See, there's Raven.
We hate her.
We're glad she's dying.
And then--
What? Marcel!
Are you playing with Monica's shoes?
You're not supposed to--
Marcel, did you poo in the shoe?
Oh, Marcel! Bad monkey!
Oh, God!
Sorry, Barry.
A little engagement gift.
I'm sure you didn't
register for that.
Who died? Who died?
Roll him over!
Come on, roll him over!
Well, we know it wasn't Dexter,
right, Marcel? Because--
Marcel?
-How could you lose him?
-I don't know!
We were watching TV,
then he pooped in Monica's shoe. . . .
Wait. He pooped in my shoe?
Which one?
I don't know.
The left one!
Which ones?
Those little clunky Amish things
you think go with everything.
Why is the air in here so negative?
Rachel lost Marcel.
Oh, no! How?
-He pooped in my shoe.
-Which one?
Those cute black ones
I wear all the time.
No, which one?
The right or left?
Because the left one is lucky.
Come on!
What am I gonna do?
All right.
You're a monkey. . .
. . .you're loose in the city.
Where do you go?
It's his first time out, so he'll
do some of the touristy things.
I'll go to Cats.
You go to the Russian Tea Room.
Oh, my God!
Come on, you guys!
He'll be home any minute.
He'll kill me!
Search the building.
You take the first and second floor.
We'll take third and fourth.
What am I gonna do?
You stay here
and just wait by the phone.
Spray Lysol in my shoe
and wait for Ross to kill you.
Does anybody want to trade?
What do you want?
Mr. Heckles, our friend lost a monkey.
Have you seen it?
I left a Belgian waffle out here.
Did you take it?
Why'd you leave it in the hall?
I wasn't ready for it.
The monkey, have you seen a monkey?
I saw Regis Philbin once.
Thank you, Mr. Heckles.
You owe me a waffle.
He's a black capuchin monkey
with a white face. . .
. . .with Russian dressing
and pickles on the side.
Thanks.
How did it go today?
Oh, great!
It went great. Really great.
Is that wine?
You want some?
Oh, I would love some.
But you know what?
Let's not drink it here.
I feel crazy.
Do you want to go to Newark?
We could. But before we go to
the murder capital of the Northeast. . .
. . .I kind of wanted
to run something by you.
You know how we
were talking before. . .
. . .about relationships and stuff. . . .
-Oh, God, Ross, I cannot do this!
-Okay, quick and painful.
Oh, God!
Okay, all right.
All right, okay.
Please don't hate me.
What? What?
You know Marcel?
I kind of lost him.
I can't believe this.
All I asked you to do was
keep him in the apartment!
I know. I'm sorry.
I guess it's partially my fault.
I shouldn't have asked you
to start off with a monkey.
I should have started you off
with a pencil.
I'm doing everything I can.
I've got everybody looking
for him and I got--
-Who is it?
-Animal Control.
-I've even got Animal Control.
-You called Animal Control?
Why? Do you not like them?
Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
I'm not allowed to have him.
If they find him,
they'll take him away from me.
Well, now, see,
you never ever told us that.
Because I never expected you
to invite them to the apartment!
Hi! Thanks for coming.
Somebody called about a monkey?
You know what? That was
a complete misunderstanding.
We thought we had a monkey,
but we didn't.
-It turned out it was a hat.
-Cat!
We checked the third floor.
No one's seen Marcel.
My uncle Marcel.
Is that who the monkey's named after?
Possession of an illegal exotic
is punishable. . .
. . .by two years in prison
and confiscation of the animal.
Oh, my God!
You'd put that poor
little creature in jail?
Remember how we talked about saying
things quietly to yourself first?
Yes, but there isn't always time.
I'm sure there's some friendly way
to reconcile this. Have a seat.
We haven't been introduced.
I'm Monica Geller.
Oh, my God, you are!
And you're Rachel Greene!
Luisa Gianetti!
Lincoln High?
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
Luisa! Oh, my God!
Monica! It's Luisa!
Luisa! From homeroom!
You have no idea who I am, do you?
Not at all.
Well, maybe that's because
you spent four years ignoring me.
Would it have been so hard to say,
''Morning, Luisa'' . . .
. . .or ''Nice overalls''?
Oh, I'm so sorry!
It's not so much you. You were fat.
You had your own problems.
But you. What a bitch!
What?
You know what?
Be that as it may.
Could you help us out here on that
monkey thing for old times' sake?
Go, Bobcats!
I could. But I won't.
If I find that monkey, he's mine.
Sorry.
Marcel?
Hi, can I help you?
We're kind of having an emergency,
and we were looking for something.
-A monkey.
-Yes, have you seen any?
No, I haven't seen a monkey.
Can you fix radiators?
Sure! Did you try turning the knob
back the other way?
Of course!
Oh. Then, no.
Taste this daiquiri.
Is there too much rum?
Just a second.
Hope you find your monkey.
Oh, no, wait!
We may not know
about radiators, per se. . .
. . .but we do have expertise
in the heating and cooling milieu.
Weren't we in the middle
of something?
But these women are very hot
and they need our help.
And they're very hot!
We can't, all right?
We're sorry.
You have no idea how sorry.
But we promised to find this monkey.
He's about yea high
and answers to the name Marcel.
So if we could get pictures of you,
it'd help us out.
From now on, you don't get
to talk to other people.
-Oh, my God!
-What?!
Something just brushed up
against my right leg.
Oh, it's okay.
It was just my left leg.
Look, Phoebe!
Oh, Marcel! Come here!
Step aside, ladies.
-What are you gonna do?
-Just a small tranquilizer.
Run, Marcel! Run, Marcel!
Damn!
Are you okay?
I think so.
Oh, gosh!
We've been all
over the neighborhood!
He's gone!
He's just gone!
-You don't know that.
-Come on! It's cold, it's dark.
He doesn't know the Village!
And now I have a broken foot.
Oh, my--
I have no monkey and a broken foot.
Thank you very much!
I've said I'm sorry,
like, a million times.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to break my foot too?
Here, I'll break my foot right now.
Oh, my God!
There, are you happy now?
Yeah, now that you kicked the sign. . .
. . .I don't miss Marcel anymore!
It's not like
I did this on purpose.
No, this is just vintage Rachel.
Things just sort of happen around you!
You're off in ''Rachel Land,''
doing your ''Rachel Thing'' . . .
. . .oblivious to people's monkeys
or to people's feelings and--
I don't even want to hear it!
Forget it, okay?
What? What?
Hey, banana man!
Oh, this is so intense!
One side of my butt is totally asleep
and the other side has no idea.
Hi! Did you order some bananas?
-What about it?
-Give me my monkey back!
I don't have a monkey.
-Then what's with all the bananas?
-Potassium.
Okay, where is he?
Where is he?
What have you done to him?
That's my monkey.
That's Patty the monkey.
Are you insane?
Come here, Marcel.
Come here, Patty.
Here, monkey.
Gotcha!
-Give me my monkey back!
-That's my monkey.
Take this up with the judge.
That's not my monkey.
Just the dress is mine.
You can send it back whenever.
All right, I want my monkey!
Oh, come on, Luisa.
Sorry, prom queen.
You had to be a bitch in school,
you couldn't have been fat.
In high school,
I was the prom queen. . .
. . .and the homecoming queen
and the class president and you. . .
. . .were also there.
If you take this monkey, I'll lose. . .
. . .one of the most
important people in my life.
You can hate me if you want,
but please do not punish him.
Luisa, you have a chance
to be the bigger person here.
Take it!
Then I'll call your supervisor
and tell her. . .
. . .you shot my friend
in the ass with a dart!
It'll be nice
to get this off, won't it?
Or we can leave it on for now.
That's fine.
With the right pair of pumps,
that would be a great little outfit.
Listen. . . .
I'm sorry I was
so hard on you before--
No, come on. It was my fault.
I almost lost your--
But you got him back.
You were great.
We still have that bottle of wine.
Are you in the mood for. . .
. . .something grape?
-Sure, that would be good.
-All right.
The neighbors must be vacuuming.
Well, as long as we're. . .
. . .here. . .
. . .and not on the subject. . . .
I was thinking about. . .
. . .how mad we got
at each other before.
And I was thinking maybe
it was partially because of how we--
-Rachel?
-Barry?
I can't. I can't do it.
I can't marry Mindy.
I'm still in love with you.
We have got to start
locking that door!
This is me in The Sound of Music.
You see the von Trapp kids?
Because I'm in front of them.
I thought that was an alp.
High school was not
my favorite time.
I don't know.
I loved high school.
It was just like four years
of parties and dating and sex and--
Well, I went to boarding school
with 400 boys.
Any sex I had would've involved
a major lifestyle choice.
Doesn't it seem like
a million years ago?
My butt cheek is waking up!